harmonycentral.com 2018-08-15

# Harmony Central

**Harmony Central Privacy Policy**

**_because you've got rights_ ....**

****

**IMPORTANT COMPLIANCE STATEMENT**

**Our  current policies and business practices continue to meet or exceed GDPR requirements to support new EU data protection laws.  
**

**YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS**

Harmony Central understands your concerns as to how your information is used and shared, and we wish, by providing you with this Privacy Statement, to gain your trust and confidence in how we care for your personal information.

**DOES HARMONY CENTRAL COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

**Information you provide**

Harmony Central does not collect personally identifiable information about individuals except when such individuals specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. For example, such personally identifiable information may be gathered from a contest or sweepstakes registration, the registration process for subscription or services and in connection with content submissions, community postings (e.g., chat and forums), suggestions, voting/polling activities and transactional areas. We use this information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests or inquiries, improving our services, informing you of activities and offers of our business partners, and communicating with you regarding your subscriber account status, changes to the subscriber agreement and other matters relevant to the underlying service and/or the information collected. Upon request, Harmony Central will use reasonable efforts to allow users to update or correct personal information previously submitted to the extent such activities will not compromise privacy or security interests. Also, upon a user's request, Harmony Central will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally delete the user and his or her personal information from its database; however, it may be impossible to delete a user's entry without some residual information being retained by Harmony Central because of the nature in which backups of data are maintained.

**Information automatically provided**

We track user behavior on our website automatically. That information may include your IP address, your domain server, your type of computer, your type of web browser and statistical information regarding the pages you visit. We use this information to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners.

**Use of Cookies**

Users also should be aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of Harmony Central's internet servers or through the use of cookies. Cookies are small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and targeted advertising. Cookies are not programs that come onto a user's system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. Users should be aware that Harmony Central cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for Harmony Central. If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, users should note that cookies may be necessary to provide the user with certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on the Harmony Central site.

**DOES HARMONY CENTRAL SHARE THE INFORMATION IT COLLECTS?**

**Companies offering promotions, products or services**

Personally identifiable information on individual users will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection. At such points of collection, the user will have the opportunity to indicate whether he or she would like to "opt out" of receiving promotional and/or marketing information about other products, services and offerings from Harmony Central and/or any third parties. In addition, Harmony Central occasionally sends e-mail promotions out to our subscribers on behalf of third-party sponsors. In this instance, unless you have given us your permission to do so, we will not send these types of promotions to you and we don't share your personally identifiable information with these third parties. Upon request, Harmony Central will allow any user to opt out of promotional contacts at any time.

**Service providers**

Harmony Central may disclose information about individual users to third parties who provide services to Harmony Central and who agree to maintain the confidentiality of such information in accordance with this Privacy Statement. These third parties may provide a variety of services to Harmony Central, including, without limitation, fulfilling product orders, managing or hosting the website, helping create new content and promotions for the site, and sending or coordinating the sending of marketing communications to users have consented to receive such materials. In situations where a user has supplied his or her information in connection with a question or request for information about a product or service offered by one of our business partners, we may also send the information he or she has supplied to the business partners that offer such products or services.

**Aggregate information**

We may share aggregated demographic information about our user base as well as aggregated user behavior data with third parties, such as advertisers. We do not link, however, this data with personally identifiable information.

**Content partners and links to other websites**

We may provide or link to content that is created by a third-party partner website that offers products and services. Such third-party sites may collect information in order to facilitate that transaction process or make the use of the content more productive and efficient. In these circumstances, the information collected may be shared between Harmony Central and these third parties. Users should consult the privacy policies posted on these third party websites as well. In addition, our website may contain links to third party websites to which we have no affiliation. Harmony Central does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on these third party websites.

**Subscription and/ or registration-based services**

Users should be aware that Harmony Central may sometimes permit third parties to offer subscription and/or registration-based services through a Harmony Central site. Harmony Central is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties and users should check the applicable privacy policy of such party when providing personally identifiable information.

**Information you publicly post**

Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., user name, e-mail address) on the forums, classifieds or in the chat areas of the Harmony Central sites, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in the user's communication, can be collected and correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Harmony Central. Please do not post any personal information on Harmony Central forums or classifieds or in the chat areas that you expect to keep private.

**Disclosures required by law**

Harmony Central will disclose information about individual users to governmental or judicial authorities or law enforcement agencies, or to other individuals or entities in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes. Further, Harmony Central may share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or suspected fraud, or to enforce or apply the terms and conditions of this Statement.

**Business transfers**

If Harmony Central is acquired by or merged with another company, or if Harmony Central decides to sell all or substantially all of its assets or shares to another company, Harmony Central may transfer personally-identifiable information about you to that company as part of that transaction. Harmony Central will notify you in the event that your personally-identifiable information is transferred under these circumstances and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Financial information**

To the extent that we may collect personally identifiable financial information, such as credit card information, that you have volunteered to us in order to conduct a transaction through our website, such financial information would only be shared with either the government, if we are so required by law (see above), or third party service providers or partners who are assisting Harmony Central in processing your requested transaction, which transaction requires the use of your financial information, such as a sale or license of products. Under the latter circumstance, such third parties would only receive your personally identifiable financial information upon agreeing to maintain its confidentiality and to the terms of this Privacy Statement.

**With your consent**

Other than as explained above, Harmony Central will notify you when information about you may be provided to third parties, and you will have the option to prevent such information sharing.

**WHAT SECURITY PRECAUTIONS ARE TAKEN TO PROTECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

This website incorporates appropriate safeguards to protect the security, integrity, completeness, accuracy and privacy of the personal information we have collected, and we have put in place reasonable precautions to protect information from loss, misuse and alteration. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as required and only authorized individuals have access to the information you provide us. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Statement.

You hereby acknowledge that Harmony Central is not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the Internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.

**Collection Of Children’s Personal Information**

Harmony Central is committed to protecting the privacy of children. The Site is not directed to children under the age of 13, and Harmony Central does not collect or maintain personal information online from children we actually know are under the age of 13. Should we discover that we have collected personal information online from a child who is under 13, we will promptly delete that personal information. If you have concerns over the collection of children’s personal information online, please contact us at the address below.

**TERMS AND MODIFICATIONS TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT**

By using the website, you signify your agreement to the terms of our Privacy Statement. If you do not agree with these terms, you should not use the site. Harmony Central may modify this Privacy Statement at any time. If a material change is made to this Privacy Statement and/or the way we use our users' personally identifiable information, then we will post prominent notice of the nature of such change on the first page of this Privacy Statement and also on our home page. You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Statement periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it. Your continued use of the site indicates your assent to any changes to this Privacy Statement. This Privacy Statement is applicable to all web sites under the .harmony-central.com and .harmonycentral.com domains.

In addition to the strides Harmony Central has made to ensure GDPR compliance, we are evaluating outside security vendors to ensure our current policies and business practices continue to meet or exceed GDPR requirements. 

**CONTACT DETAILS**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the privacy practices of this website, or if you want to exercise any of the rights that you are given under this Privacy Statement, you can contact:

Harmony Central

309 Plus Park Blvd.

Nashville, TN 37217

Updated: May 29, 2018
